<recipes>
    <recipe>
        <name>Easy Chicken Yassa</name>
        <difficulty>easy</difficulty>
        <duration unit="min">82</duration>
        <ingredients>
            <ingredient amount="4" unit="pcs">Chicken Quarters (thighs and legs attached)</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="1" unit="tsp">Salt</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="1" unit="tsp">Cayenne Pepper</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="1" unit="tsp">Garlic granules or garlic powder</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="2" unit="tsp">Ground black pepper, divided</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="2" unit="tsp">Dried parsley, divided</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="4" unit="pcs">Large onions, thinly sliced</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="3" unit="pcs">Cloves of garlic, minced</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="3" unit="tsp">Dijon mustard</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="1" unit="pcs">Lemon, juiced</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="2" unit="tsp">Olive oil</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="1.5" unit="cups">Olive oil</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="2" unit="bay">Leaves</ingredient>
            <ingredient amount="0.25" unit="cups">Green olives</ingredient>
        </ingredients>
        <steps>
            <step order="1">Preheat the oven to 400째F</step>
            <step order="2">Score the chicken: To do this, make two slits in the chicken. One on the leg end and another on the thigh end. This allows for the flavor of seasoning to penetrate deeper into the chicken.</step>
            <step order="3">Season and marinate the chicken: In a small mixing bowl combine the salt, cayenne pepper, garlic granules, 1 teaspoon black pepper, and 1 teaspoon dried parsley. In a large bowl, season the chicken on both sides with the spice mix. Cover with some plastic wrap, set aside and let marinade for 10 minutes.</step>
            <step order="4">Prepare the onions: In a large mixing bowl, combine the onions, garlic, Dijon mustard, remaining 1 teaspoon dried parsley, remaining 1 teaspoon black pepper, and lemon juice.</step>
            <step order="5">Roast the chicken: Place the chicken quarters on a sheet pan and bake at 400째F for 20 to 30 minutes until golden brown and crispy. If you insert a fork near to the joints you should have clear juices flowing out. If you have an instant read thermometer, insert it into the thickest part of the chicken and it should read between 165째F-175째F.</step>
            <step order="6">Make the onion mustard sauce: In a large pan over medium-heat, add 2 tablespoons of olive oil and the onion mustard mixture. Cook, stirring occasionally, about 10 minutes. The onions should be translucent and start to take on a golden-brown color. Add the chicken stock, bay leaves, and olives to the onions. Reduce the heat to medium-low and simmer for 5 minutes. The onions should be golden and caramelized and the stock should have thickened slightly.</step>
            <step order="7">Add cooked chicken to onion mustard sauce: Once the chicken is done, using tongs, nestle the chicken quarters into the onion mustard sauce. Let the chicken simmer in the sauce for another 5-7 minutes then turn the heat off. now you have what looks like a rich stew.</step>
            <step order="8">Serve: Serve the chicken yassa with white rice or any other grain of your choosing.</step>
        </steps>
    </recipe>
</recipes>